If you think about open AI and some of the new AI stuff
that's going on there.
One of the strategies that's becoming more prevalent
is rather than trying to buy these AI companies
that let's say they've got 30 geniuses that work there
and trying to buy that company for a billion dollars,
they just look at the top 20 of the 30 people.
Maybe they got diluted because of the way
the VCs ran the deal or whatever,
and then they just say, hey, I'll give you,
and you've seen these $100 million signing bonuses
probably flying around on Instagram.
And it sounds absurd, but it actually is more efficient
to give one person or the four key people
in the business $100 million
than buy the business for four billion.
It's just a pure allocation of capital play.
And so from a buy versus build,
if you can strip the talent out
and they can keep the relationships
and then you can rebuild it,
that'll be the most efficient way to do it.